Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids: Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：是的，是的，队长。
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：
是的，是的，船长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
Hey, I'm expecting
a 50-cent rebate check.
嘿嘿，我期待着
50 美分的回扣支票。
Give me, give me,
give me, give me.
给我，给我，
给我，给我。
Sorry, no check.
抱歉，没有检查。
But I've got this.
但我有这个。
Oh, correspondence
in a bottle, ay?
噢，信件
在瓶子里，是吗？
"Ahoy, Eugene.
“嘿，尤金。
I'm so proud you followed
your old grandpa's peg leg
and became a pirate
我很自豪你关注了
你老爷爷的假腿
并成为一名海盗
that I'll be sailing by
for a ship's inspection.
我将航行经过
用于船舶检查。
That vessel better be
well-oiled or you'll be dancing
the short plank jig.
那艘船最好是
加油，否则你会跳舞
短木板夹具。
Happy lootin',
Grandpa Redbeard."
快乐的抢劫，
红胡子爷爷。”
: Ah!
：啊！
I didn't know your grandpa
was a pirate, Mr. Krabs?
我不认识你爷爷
是海盗吗，蟹老板？
Aye... I come from
a whole family of pirates.
是的...我来自
整个海盗家族。
Gramps used to say:
爷爷常说：
"The Krabs clan
has been pirates
“蟹蟹一族
曾经是海盗
for as long as
we've had claws."
只要
我们有爪子。”
And he wanted me to
be a pirate, too.
他希望我
也成为一名海盗。
One day you'll be
a plundering pirate
有一天你会成为
掠夺的海盗
just like your
old granddad here.
就像你的一样
老爷爷在这里。
Aargh.
啊啊。
Krabs: So I bought me a ship,
hired a crew...
蟹老板：所以我买了一艘船，
雇了一个船员...
Aargh!
啊啊！
...and for years I drifted
the high seas as a pirate.
......多年来我一直在漂泊
作为海盗在公海上航行。
And booty did abound.
战利品确实比比皆是。
I started to notice
a recurring theme.
我开始注意到
一个反复出现的主题。
Oh!
哦！
...I just wasn't turning
enough profit
……我只是没有转身
足够的利润
so I fired me crew,
and sold me ship.
所以我解雇了我的船员
并把船卖给了我。
'Twas also the last time
I saw me granddad.
这也是最后一次
我看见了我爷爷。
Aargh, if it ain't me
pirate grandson.
啊啊，如果不是我的话
海盗孙子。
Well, actually Grandpa,
I just sold...
嗯，其实爷爷，
我刚卖...
You know how proud
if makes me
你知道有多骄傲
如果让我
to see me only
grandson continuing in
the family business.
只见我一个人
孙子继续
家族企业。
:
Eh, yeah, Grandpa...
：
呃，是啊，爷爷……
And I'll be keeping me
eye on your career
我会保留我
关注你的职业生涯
to see how you progress.
看看你进步如何。
Just remember, the only rule in
the pirate's code of honor is
请记住，唯一的规则是
海盗的荣誉准则是
never  tell a lie.
永远不要说谎。
For all he knows
据他所知
the Krusty Krab
is a pirate ship.
蟹堡王
是一艘海盗船。
If he were to find
out the truth
如果他找到
说出真相
it'd break his salty,
barnacle-encrusted heart.
它会打破他的咸味，
布满藤壶的心。
Why don't we just make
the Krusty Krab look
like a pirate ship.
我们为什么不直接做
蟹堡王造型
就像海盗船一样。
Hm, not a bad idea, boy.
嗯，这主意不错，孩子。
But we're gonna need
a first-rate crew.
但我们需要
一流的船员。
We got Squidward- and I could
get Patrick to join up.
我们得到了章鱼哥——我可以
让帕特里克加入。
Yeah.
是的。
Krabs: All right, me hearties-
螃蟹：好吧，亲爱的——
get this one thing clear.
把这一件事弄清楚。
If Grandpa Redbeard is ever
gonna believe I'm a pirate
如果红胡子爷爷曾经
相信我是一名海盗
ye land lubbers is gonna have
to pass for a pirate crew.
你们这些旱鸭子将会有
冒充海盗团伙。
Which means...
这意味着...
I want you to  look
like a pirate.
我想让你看看
像海盗一样。
I want you to  talk
like a pirate.
我想让你说话
像海盗一样。
Swarthy!
黝黑的！
: I mean,
shiver me timbers.
：我的意思是，
让我颤抖。
But most importantly
但最重要的是
I want you to
我要你
smell  like a pirate.
闻起来像海盗。
Ohh.
哦。
Very convincing, Patrick.
非常有说服力，帕特里克。
And as me crew...
而作为我的船员...
You'd be making the Krusty Krab
into an imitation pirate ship.
你会做蟹堡王
进入一艘仿海盗船。
Now let's get this
restaurant ready to sail.
现在让我们得到这个
餐厅准备起航。
Krabs: Way to go, fellers.
螃蟹：干得好，伙计们。
Grandpa: Whee... Ha!
爷爷：呼……哈！
He's coming.
他来了。
Hold me, boy.
抱紧我，男孩。
Eugene, me boy.
尤金，我的孩子。
Ah, it's good to see
you and your ship
啊，很高兴看到
你和你的船
after so many moons.
经过这么多个月。
'Twas beginning to think you was
lying to your old granddad.
我开始以为你是
对你的老爷爷撒谎。
:
Oh, I... Ehh...
：
哦，我……呃……
Mm, ha  .
嗯，哈。
So have you met me hearties?
那么你见过我的心吗？
Hmm...
唔...
...You call this a pirate crew?
……你管这叫海贼团？
They more resemble jellyfishers
than swarthy brine skimmers.
它们更像水母
比黑色的盐水撇油器。
Um...
嗯...
I'm just yanking
your chain, boy.
我只是拉扯
你的链子，孩子。
You look like a fine
pirate crew.
你看起来像个好人
海盗船员。
Whoo.
呼。
Now let's see what this
rusty old pelican can do.
现在让我们看看这是什么
生锈的老鹈鹕可以做到。
Let's sail!
我们扬帆起航吧！
Aye sir.
是的，先生。
Ahoy, Capt'n.
嘿，船长。
We be catching a mighty gale
from the Northeast.
我们正遭遇一场大风
来自东北。
Indeed, indeed, and...
确实，确实，而且……
And just look at the
treacherous surf in our path.
只要看看
我们的道路上有危险的海浪。
Oh, that salty sea air
be so thick
哦，咸咸的海洋空气
这么厚
you can almost
taste it.
你几乎可以
尝尝它。
I'd better take the helm and
guide us to safer waters.
我最好掌舵
引导我们前往更安全的水域。
Aye, that'd be a wicked sounding
wind out there, eh, Granddad?
是的，这听起来很邪恶
外面有风吗，呃，爷爷？
I said, "Aye...
我说：“是啊……
That'd be a wicked
sounding wind out there."
那将是一个恶人
外面有风声。”
Oh.
哦。
There is it.
就是这样。
That wind storm
I mentioned earlier...
那一场风暴
我之前提到过...
And, oh, apparently
the cabin is haunted as well.
而且，哦，显然
小屋也闹鬼。
What's a hair net doing
on a pirate ship?
发网有什么作用
在海盗船上？
Any pirate knows that the
majority of his daily nutrition
任何海盗都知道
他的大部分日常营养
comes from whatever
hair or skin flakes
来自任何事物
头发或皮肤碎片
fall off of the cook
and into the stew.
从厨师身上掉下来
并放入炖菜中。
This hair net
is depriving your crew
这个发网
剥夺了你的船员的权利
of their essential nutrients.
他们的必需营养素。
Eh... Just a sec.
呃……等一下。
Look out, Grandpa,
we're under attack.
爷爷，你要小心，
我们受到攻击。
Aye, look at the size
of that beast.
嗯，看尺寸
那只野兽的。
Not to worry,
Granddad.
不用担心，
爷爷。
Ah-ha, that's the stuff.
啊哈，就是这个东西。
: Hee-yah!
: 嘿嘿！
Eh, good toss,
hey, Granddad?
嗯，抛得好，
嘿，爷爷？
Oh, nothing, look.
哦，没什么，看看。
Ha-ha-ha-ha-
ha-ha-ha
哈哈哈哈哈哈——
哈哈哈
that's me boy.
这就是我，男孩。
All: Hooray!
全体：万岁！
Whoo-hoo!
呼呼！
Sounds like we got a prize.
听起来我们好像得到了奖品。
Ready, Squidward?
准备好了吗，章鱼哥？
You owe me big time, Mr. Krabs.
你欠我很大的情，蟹老板。
Krabs: Aye, take that, ya...
螃蟹：是的，接受这个，你……
Ya scurvy dog, ya.
是坏血病狗，是的。
Whoo!
呼！
Check the size of it, Granddad.
爷爷，检查一下它的大小。
Granddad, check the...
爷爷，检查一下...
Granddad?
爷爷？
Trouble approaching quick.
麻烦很快就来了。
Approximately 10 clicks
off the starboard bow.
大约 10 次点击
位于右舷船头。
Man your
battle stations.
男人你的
战斗站。
Oh, no, if Granddad
sees something
哦，不，如果爷爷
看到一些东西
it must be the real deal.
这一定是货真价实的。
What do you got,
cotton in your ears... Move!
你有什么，
耳朵里有棉花……动起来！
What exactly are we dealing
with, Grandpa?
我们到底在处理什么
和，爷爷？
Something more hideous
than I've ever seen.
更可怕的东西
比我见过的还要多。
A raving gargantuan banshee
一只狂暴的巨型女妖
with a coarse matted mane
of tangled locks.
有着粗糙的乱蓬蓬的鬃毛
缠结的锁。
Ugh.
啊。
Sounds repulsive.
听起来很令人反感。
Yeah, it must be destroyed.
是啊，必须毁掉。
Here, see for yourself.
在这里，你自己看看。
Go get it, Granddad.
去拿吧，爷爷。
Wait a minute...
等一下...
What kind of disgusting
horrible aberration dare
invade me vessel?
什么样的恶心
可怕的畸变敢
入侵我的船？
Dad!
爸爸！
That disgusting
horrible thing...
那个恶心的
可怕的事情...
is me daughter.
是我女儿。
Open up!
打开！
Prepare to meet
yer maker, sea witch.
准备见面
你的创造者，海女巫。
Krabs: No!
蟹蟹：不！
What are ya doing?
你在做什么？
Oh, I... I was, uh...
哦，我...我是，呃...
Just checkin' the cannon,
making sure it was loaded.
只是检查大炮，
确保它已加载。
Papier-maché?
纸浆？
What is this?
这是什么？
I can explain...
我可以解释一下...
Dad!
爸爸！
Now it's even more angry.
现在更是愤怒了。
Don't worry, I have
it under control.
别担心，我有
它受到控制。
Daddy!
爸爸！
Pearl, could ya
pipe down?
珍珠，可以吗
管道下降？
Your Great Granddad
Redbeard is in there.
你的曾祖父
红胡子就在里面。
What's with
the lame outfit?
有什么
蹩脚的衣服？
What... Oh, never
mind that.
什么...哦，从来没有
请介意。
Just go home.
回家吧。
Aargh...
啊啊……
I bet you're
wondering about that.
我打赌你是
想知道这一点。
Well, you're darn
tootin' I am.
好吧，你真该死
我也是。
Do you mind?
你介意吗？
What kind of ship
are you running here?
什么样的船
你跑到这里了吗？
Just a second.
稍等一下。
Grr... Aargh.
呃……啊啊。
Aargh!
啊啊！
Now, Granddad,
there's a simple explanation.
现在，爷爷，
有一个简单的解释。
I've smelled
a lot of stinky things
我闻过
很多臭东西
but nothing smells stinkier
但没有什么比这更臭了
than a lie.
比谎言。
There's a code that
all pirates live by.
有一段代码
所有海盗都以此为生。
You knows what
it is, don't ya?
你知道什么
是的，不是吗？
Of course
I do, Granddad.
当然
我愿意，爷爷。
Well then... Say it.
那么……说吧。
OK, it's...
好吧，这是...
It's, it's...
这是、这是...
A pirate never lies.
海盗从不说谎。
And I've been
a dirty liar.
我已经
一个肮脏的骗子。
Everything you've seen is a lie.
你所看到的一切都是谎言。
This sail is a lie.
这帆是一个谎言。
This crew is a lie.
这个船员是个谎言。
Grr...
呃……
Even this ship is a lie.
甚至这艘船也是一个谎言。
All of it.
所有这一切。
All a lie.
都是谎言。
Krabby Patties: $2.00.
蟹黄饼：2.00 美元。
Krusty Combo: $3.99.
Krusty 组合：3.99 美元。
Coral bits: $1.95?
珊瑚块：1.95 美元？
So you see, Granddad...
所以你看，爷爷...
I'm no pirate.
我不是海盗。
Just a lowly restaurant owner.
只是一个卑微的餐馆老板。
I'm sorry I failed ye.
很抱歉我让你们失望了。
Failed me,
boy?
让我失败了，
男孩？
Why, I couldn't
be more proud.
为什么，我不能
更加自豪。
Look at yer
ludicrous prices.
看看你
可笑的价格。
Now that's real piracy.
现在这才是真正的盗版。
Ya done good, boy-o.
你做得很好，男孩。
Really?
真的吗？
Thanks, Granddad.
谢谢，爷爷。
Well, you can thank
yourself, lad.
嗯，你可以感谢
你自己，小伙子。
You created this
dynasty on yer own.
你创造了这个
王朝靠你自己。
Ha-ha, now, I'll be
taking me leave, boy.
哈哈，现在我就
带我离开吧，孩子。
Good-bye, Granddad.
再见，爷爷。
What an honest man.
多么诚实的一个人啊。
Grandpa: I hope
you don't mind, boy-o
爷爷：我希望
你不介意，男孩
but I helped myself to
a little bit of your booty.
但我帮助自己
你的一点点战利品。
I knew I got me talent
from someone.
我知道我有天赋
来自某人。
: Ah,
gah-gah-gah-gah-gah-gah.
：啊，
嘎嘎嘎嘎。
SpongeBob: ♪ Workin'
at the Krusty Krab ♪
海绵宝宝：♪ 工作中
在蟹堡蟹店♪
♪ Workin' at the Krusty Krab,
la, la, la... ♪
♪ 在蟹堡王工作，
啦啦啦……♪
Ooh.
哦。
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
Squidward.
章鱼哥。
Squidward,
are you OK?
章鱼哥，
你还好吗？
Oh, I couldn't be better.
哦，我不能更好了。
Mister Krabs!
蟹蟹先生！
It happened again,
Mr. Krabs.
事情又发生了，
蟹老板。
What are you
talking about?
你在说什么？
It's Squidward.
这是章鱼哥。
What is it about the third
Wednesday of every month
第三个是什么
每个月的星期三
that makes Squidward so happy?
这让章鱼哥如此高兴？
Psst, Squidward...
嘘，章鱼哥……
Roger, is that you?
罗杰，是你吗？
Tonight's the big night.
今晚是个重要的夜晚。
SpongeBob: These camouflage
outfits should help us find out
海绵宝宝：这些伪装
服装应该可以帮助我们找到答案
what Squidward's secret
Wednesday secret is.
章鱼哥的秘密是什么
星期三的秘密是。
Hello, brother Roger.
你好，罗杰兄弟。
Come right in,
brother Squidward.
进来吧，
章鱼哥。
Thank you.
谢谢。
This almost makes the other
这几乎让其他
353 days worth living for.
353天值得活下去。
For centuries...
几个世纪以来...
Cephalopods have had
but one nemesis.
头足类动物有
但有一个克星。
Let he among you
让他在你们中间
who wishes to join the lodge
谁想加入旅馆
face your greatest fear.
面对你最大的恐惧。
Cantankerous moray eelius
脾气暴躁的海鳗
Huh?
啊？
I'll never forget
my initiation ceremony.
我永远不会忘记
我的入会仪式。
Yeah!
是的！
Way to go.
一路走好。
SpongeBob, Patrick,
did you follow me here?
海绵宝宝、帕特里克、
你跟着我到这里来了吗？
Brother Squidward?
章鱼哥？
For thousands of years
no outsiders
几千年来
没有外人
have witnessed
this sacred initiation.
见证过
这个神圣的启蒙。
You have desecrated
the sanctity
你亵渎了
神圣性
of this lodge.
这家旅馆的。
:
But, but, I, I, I...
：
但是，但是，我，我，我……
Oh, I can't believe it.
哦，我简直不敢相信。
They kicked me out of
the Cephalopod Lodge.
他们把我踢出了
头足类动物旅馆。
Do we get to
join the lodge?
我们能到达吗
加入旅馆吗？
Were you dropped on your head
when you were a baby?
你是否被摔在头上
当你还是个婴儿的时候？
Psychic powers.
心灵力量。
Hey, where's Patrick?
嘿，帕特里克在哪儿？
Maybe he got
to join the lodge?
也许他得到了
加入小屋？
Or maybe not.
或者也许不是。
They didn't let you
join either?
他们没有让你
要么加入？
Nah, I found
the institution
不，我发现了
该机构
had nothing
left to offer me.
一无所有
留下来向我提供。
I was stagnating.
我停滞不前。
Hey, where's Squidward?
嘿，章鱼哥在哪里？
Hold on, um...
坚持住，嗯...
Found Squidward,
hmm...  .
发现章鱼哥，
嗯……
The last thing in my life
I really enjoyed
我生命中最后一件事
我真的很喜欢
and SpongeBob ruined it too.
海绵宝宝也毁了它。
at least you still
have the hat.
至少你还在
有帽子。
Yeah  ?
是的  ？
I do, don't I?
我愿意，不是吗？
You still have
your robes.
你还有
你的长袍。
You still have
your underwear.
你还有
你的内衣。
Squidward: No!
章鱼哥：不！
You can look now.
你现在可以看看。
Don't you worry,
Squidward.
你不用担心，
章鱼哥。
I'm sure if Patrick
and I just explain
what happened
我确信如果帕特里克
我只是解释一下
发生了什么事
they're sure to let you back in.
他们一定会让你回来的。
What is it?
它是什么？
Oh, it's you two.
噢，是你们两个。
We just came to explain
that Squidward had no idea
我们只是来解释一下
章鱼哥不知道
that we followed him
to the lodge.
我们跟着他
到旅馆。
So it's not his fault.
所以这不是他的错。
Yeah, not his fault.
是的，不是他的错。
Then whose fault was it?
那么这又是谁的错呢？
Is it my fault?
是我的错吗？
No, it wasn't
your fault, Patrick.
不，不是的
你的错，帕特里克。
Thanks, SpongeBob.
谢谢，海绵宝宝。
And it wasn't
your fault either.
事实并非如此
也是你的错。
Well, if it
wasn't your fault
好吧，如果是的话
不是你的错
and it wasn't
Squidward's fault,
whose fault was it?
它不是
都是章鱼哥的错
这是谁的错？
Uhh...
呃...
Maybe it's
your fault.
也许是
你的错。
Squidward is never allowed
in this lodge again.
章鱼哥是绝对不被允许的
再次来到这个小屋。
SpongeBob, are they letting me
back in the lodge?
海绵宝宝，他们让我吗
回到小屋？
No, you can't set
foot in the lodge.
不，你不能设置
脚走进小屋。
Ever!
曾经！
Ohh...
哦...
Now that you two have ruined
the last good thing in my life
既然你们两个已经毁了
我生命中最后的好事
I think I'll go home
我想我会回家
and slam my head
in the door... Repeatedly.
并猛击我的头
在门里……反复。
SpongeBob: Squidward, wait.
海绵宝宝：章鱼哥，等等。
I'm sorry we got you kicked out
of your lodge.
很抱歉我们把你赶了出来
你的小屋。
Is there anything I can do
to make it up to you?
有什么我可以做的吗
来弥补你吗？
No- why didn't you just
make up your own dumb club
不-你为什么不直接
组建你自己的愚蠢俱乐部
instead of
ruining mine?
而不是
毁了我的？
That's it!
就是这样！
Squidward, we'll make
our own club.
章鱼哥，我们会做
我们自己的俱乐部。
And it'll be so much
better than that dumb old
"Ceplafalehflopop" Lodge.
而且会这么多
比那个愚蠢的老头好
“Ceplafalehflopop”旅馆。
And  you  can be our leader.
你可以成为我们的领导者。
How great does that sound,
oh, mighty one?
这听起来多么棒，
噢，强大的一个？
Want to join
our club, Patrick?
想加入
我们的俱乐部，帕特里克？
Dog pile on Squidward.
狗堆在章鱼哥身上。
SpongeBob: Squidward,
you're the lodge expert.
海绵宝宝：章鱼哥，
你是旅馆专家。
What do we do first?
我们首先做什么？
Say good-bye.
告别。
Good-bye.
再见。
Morons.
白痴。
So anyway, Squidward-
所以无论如何，章鱼哥——
I was thinking
we should be working on our
secret lodge initiations.
我在想
我们应该致力于我们的
秘密小屋的入会仪式。
Hey.
嘿。
Patrick and I have come up
with a secret handshake.
帕特里克和我已经上来了
秘密握手。
Secret!
秘密！
Patty cake, patty cake,
sailor man.
馅饼，馅饼，
水手人。
Bake me a cake
as fast...
给我烤个蛋糕
一样快...
Squidward: SpongeBob!
章鱼哥：海绵宝宝！
That's not
a secret handshake.
那不是
秘密握手。
Everybody knows
patty cake.
大家都知道
肉饼蛋糕。
Not the way we do it.
不是我们做事的方式。
We don't use
our pinkies.
我们不使用
我们的小指。
: Out!
： 出去！
I don't think Squidward
wants to join our lodge.
我不认为章鱼哥
想加入我们的旅馆。
Oh, sure he does.
哦，当然他知道。
He just needs a little push.
他只需要一点推动。
Oh, what now?
哦，现在怎么办？
: I'm coming.
: 我来了。
What do you... Great.
你做什么...太好了。
Must be one of
SpongeBob's pranks.
必须是其中之一
海绵宝宝的恶作剧。
Let's move.
我们走吧。
OK, we can let
him out now.
好的，我们可以让
现在他出去了。
Are you insane?
你疯了吗？
You kidnapped me?
你绑架了我？
Oh, we didn't kidnap you.
哦，我们没有绑架你。
We just brought
you here for...
我们刚刚带来了
你来这里是为了...
Initiation.
引发。
What kind
of initiation?
什么样的
的启蒙？
A very special initiation.
一个非常特别的启蒙。
Oh, boy,
look at the time,
gotta run.
哦，男孩，
看看时间，
得跑了。
Oh.
哦。
Would you care to go
first, brother Patrick?
你愿意去吗
首先，帕特里克兄弟？
After you,
brother SpongeBob.
在你之后，
海绵宝宝弟弟。
La...
拉...
Ah, oh, ooh!
啊，哦，哦！
"Bruthuh Pathrith?"
“布鲁图·帕特里斯？”
Brother SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝兄弟？
"Bruthu Squidwuth"?
“布鲁图乌贼”？
Oh.
哦。
What's this, can it be?
这是什么，可以吗？
My lodge robes.
我的小屋长袍。
I'm back in the lodge.
我回到小屋了
I gotta try 'em on.
我得试穿一下。
Huh- this can't be right.
哈——这不对。
These aren't
my Cephalopod robes.
这些不是
我的头足类长袍。
They sure aren't.
他们肯定不是。
They're your uniform
for your new lodge.
它们是你的制服
为你的新小屋。
Welcome to the first
official meeting of...
欢迎来到第一
正式会议...
The Feather Friends.
羽毛之友。
Feather Friends?
羽友？
Somebody already had
Feather Buddies.
已经有人有过
羽毛伙伴们。
Yeah, those Feather
Buddies better hope
是的，那些羽毛
小伙伴们更希望
they don't run into us
in a dark alley.
他们不会碰到我们
在一个黑暗的小巷里。
Ahh!
啊！
I don't want to be
a Feather Buddy!
我不想成为
一个羽毛伙伴！
Do you still wanna
be a Feather Friend?
你还想吗
成为羽毛的朋友吗？
Grrr...
咕噜……
No.
不。
Squidward, I hadn't
realized how special
your lodge was to you.
章鱼哥，我没有
意识到有多特别
你的小屋是给你的。
I'll get you back in that club.
我会让你回到那个俱乐部。
And I know just
how to do it.
我知道只是
怎么做。
Everything we need
is in this drawer.
我们需要的一切
就在这个抽屉里。
Squidward: A sock?
章鱼哥：袜子？
Not just a sock, a disguise.
不仅仅是一只袜子，更是一种伪装。
Patrick and I will climb
inside the sock
帕特里克和我会攀登
袜子里面
and pretend to be
a giant Albino eel.
并假装是
一条巨大的白化鳗鱼
We will then gain
entrance to the lodge
那么我们将获得
小屋的入口
and frighten everyone inside.
并吓坏里面的每个人。
Once they're good and terrified
一旦他们表现良好并感到害怕
you, Squidward, will storm in,
defeat that giant eel
你，章鱼哥，会冲进来，
打败那条巨型鳗鱼
and rescue all
of the lodge members.
并营救所有人
分会成员。
You'll be a hero, Squidward.
你会成为英雄的，章鱼哥。
They'll have to let you
back in the lodge.
他们必须让你
回到小屋。
Hm, it's genius.
嗯，真是天才。
But I see one flaw
in your plan.
但我看到一个缺陷
在你的计划中。
One  flaw?
一个缺陷？
That sock is
way too small.
那只袜子是
太小了。
Yeah, it is.
是的，确实如此。
Time to break out
the heavy artillery.
是时候爆发了
重炮。
That's what
I'm talking about.
就是这样
我说的是。
SpongeBob: OK, Squidward,
just give us five minutes
and then do your stuff.
海绵宝宝：好的，章鱼哥，
给我们五分钟
然后做你的事情。
French Man: Five minutes later.
法国人：五分钟后。
This is ridiculous.
这太荒谬了。
No one is dumb enough to believe
没有人傻到相信
SpongeBob and Patrick are a...
海绵宝宝和帕特里克是...
A giant Albino eel?
巨型白化鳗鱼？
Eel: Roar!
鳗鱼：咆哮！
Roar!
吼！
Unbelievable.
难以置信。
Squidward!
章鱼哥！
There's a giant Albino
eel on the loose.
有一个巨大的白化病
鳗鱼散了。
Ahem, do not worry.
咳咳，别担心。
I will save you.
我会救你的。
Begone, foul beast
走开，邪恶的野兽
or I will smite thee.
不然我就打你。
SpongeBob: Aargh.
海绵宝宝：啊啊。
...Oof!
...钱币！
All: Yay!
全体：耶！
: Squidward,
Squidward, Squidward...
： 章鱼哥，
章鱼哥，章鱼哥……
...Squidward, Squidward
……章鱼哥，章鱼哥
Squidward, Squidward.
章鱼哥，章鱼哥。
SpongeBob/Squidward:
Yes, yes!
海绵宝宝/章鱼哥：
是的，是的！
Way to go Squidward.
去鱿鱼哥吧。
It worked.
它起作用了。
Heh-heh...
呵呵...
Whoa-whoa... Whoa.
哇-哇...哇。
Don't worry, Squidward.
别担心，章鱼哥。
We still have
the Feather Friends.
我们还有
羽毛之友。
But you'll have to pass
the initiation again.
但你必须通过
再次启动。
Ah, ahh!
啊啊啊！